we all tell lies that's what makes us
human like going to the bathroom or
slowly dying
but keeping track of those lies can seem
like a full-time job
and who has time for that as i was
saying harvard
was a blast i thought you said you went
to princeton
introducing fibbit fibbit is a wearable
device that remembers your lies so you
don't have to
you said you went to princeton i
did go to princeton i went to harvard
last weekend for a party
whether you're telling a white lie okay
jackie you next pinkerton
or the blue album you love weezer's
entire discography
oh my two favorite weeds are albums you
know i love them both too much to choose
or something more do you really have to
go to canada
every weekend you have two children with
your
second wife babe the firm needs me
and so do our two children fibbit uses
polygraph
technology to determine when you're
telling a lie
once fibbit's internal liar sensor goes
off fibbit starts recording your lies
and filing them away for safe
keeping don't worry we won't share them
with anyone
unless you check off the i agree to all
terms and conditions box
when you sign up fibbit knows that not
all lies are spoken
for even more coverage simply connect
vivit to your phone
and let autocorrect do the work for you
just hit the did she buy it option in
your settings and will combine your eye
contact
vocal range and breathing levels into a
believability quotient
i love you
[Music]
you did good you could even lie with a
friend
it'll keep the momentum up on your
journey to the coveted 10
000th line man i've only told four lies
today
did you like that birthday gift i got
you last year yes
i loved it oh my god i picked it up just
for you dude
you really are my best friend hi i'm
hannah stocking
and i wear my fitbit to avoid minor
punishment i wear my fitbit to keep
track of all my lies
i wear my fibbit so that i don't have to
listen to alternative rock music
i wear my fitbit to be a better lawyer
and a better father of
[Music]
[Applause]
two
ah